(Sheldon:)Just out of curiosity, Penny,
(Sheldon:)if this experiment does
make us fall in love,
(Sheldon:)would you drive me
to Lake Geneva, Wisconsin
(Sheldon:)for Gary Con?
(Sheldon:)It's the only convention
celebrating
(Sheldon:)the life and work of Gary Gygax,
(Sheldon:)the co-creator
of Dungeons and Dragons.
(Penny:)You know what?
(Penny:)I can honestly say
if we fall in love,
(Penny:)not only will I drive you there,
I will buy you
(Penny:)all the dragon T-shirts
you want.
(Sheldon:)Okay, babe, let's do this.
(Raj:)You guys are
really being calm
(Raj:)about Penny and Sheldon
doing this thing.
(stammers)
If it were me,
I-I'd be a little nervous.
(Amy:)Why?
Well,
(Raj:)even if the study's nonsense,
I-I don't believe
in tempting fate.
(Raj:)Same reason I wouldn't
use a Ouija board,
(Raj:)or pick a fight
with an Asian guy.
(Raj:)He probably doesn't know karate,
but... why risk it?
(Amy:)I think we're safe.